Guide to the National Lawyers Guild Records TAM.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 2, Series IX: NLG v. AG - Reverse Discovery, 1937-1987
  - Subseries F: Material Compiled by Topic.
    - Gay Issues, 1976-1978 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Grand Jury Material, 1970-1972 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Grand Jury Material, 1970-1974 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Grand Jury Material, 1973-1977, Undated (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Grand Jury Material, 1975-1977 (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - Grand Jury Material, 1976-1978, Undated (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - Grand Jury Proceedings Collected in Connection with Black Panther Trials, 1972 (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - Handschu Case, 1981, Undated (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - Housing, [1978] (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), 1980, Undated (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - Iran, 1979, Undated (Box 259, Folder 17)
    - Ku Klux Klan: First Amendment, 1977-1980, Undated (Box 259, Folder 18)
    - Ku Klux Klan: New York Anti-Klan Network, 1980, Undated (Box 259, Folder 19)
    - Lawyer Referral, 1948-1955 (Box 259, Folder 20)
    - Legal Advisory Committee, 1953 (Box 259, Folder 21)
    - Legal Advisory Committee, 1954 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Legal Advisory Committee, 1955 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Legal Advisory Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Middle East, 1977-1980, Undated (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Middle East, 1978, Undated (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Military Law Project, 1967-Jul 1972 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Military Law Project, Sep 1972-1978, Undated (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - NLG/Study Group, 1970-1977, Undated (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Native American Issues, 1973-1978 (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Native American Issues: Committee on Native American Struggles (CONAS), 1977-1981, Undated (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Native American Issues: Indian Summer Project, 1973 (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Native American Issues: Wounded Knee, 1972-1975, Undated (Box 260, Folder 12)
    - Native American Issues: Wounded Knee Legal Defense/Offense Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 260, Folder 13)
    - Nomination of Rockefeller, Nelson as Vice-President (NLG Opposition), [1974] (Box 260, Folder 14)
    - Police Misconduct, 1976-1979, Undated (Box 260, Folder 15)
    - Prison Issues, 1971-1978, Undated (Box 260, Folder 16)
    - Prison Issues: Attica, 1971-1976 (Box 260, Folder 17)
    - Prison Issues: Women, 1972, 1978, Undated (Box 260, Folder 18)
    - Prison Issues: Women, Ad Hoc Committee on Women's Facility, 1973, 1976 (Box 260, Folder 19)
    - Prison Issues: Women, Ad Hoc Committee on Women's Facility, 1977, Undated (Box 260, Folder 20)
    - Puerto Rico, 1979, 1980, Undated (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Summer Projects, 1973-1977 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Supreme Court Nominations: Powell, Lewis and Rehnquist, William, 1971, Undated (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Tenant/Landlord Information, Undated (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam, 1979, Undated (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Women's Issues, 1973-1980, Undated (Box 261, Folder 6)
- Part 2, Series X: NLG v. AG - Research, 1937-1988
  - Subseries A: Guild History, Formal File.
    - Archives: Martin Luther King (MLK) Center, Undated (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Archives: MLK Center, Early Organizational Records (Folder 1 of 2, Part 1), 1939-1965 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Archives: MLK Center, Early Organizational Records (Folder 1 of 2, Part 2), 1937-1963 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Archives: MLK Center, Early Organizational Records (Folder 2 of 2, Part 1) - Minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Archives: MLK Center, Early Organizational Records (Folder 2 of 2, Part 2) - Minutes, 1951-1964 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Archives: MLK Center, Early Organizational Records (Folder 2 of 2, Part 3) - Resolutions, 1939-1956 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Archives: Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute, 1979-1981 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Archives: Tamiment Library Collection, 1941-1976, 1981 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Attacks on the Guild, 1962-1971, Undated (Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Detroit: Goodman, Ernest, 1937-1977 (Box 261, Folder 16)
    - History Committee, 1982 (Box 261, Folder 17)
    - History of the Guild: Index and Various Items, 1976-1978, Undated (Box 261, Folder 18)
    - Mass Defense Office, 1968-1970 (Box 261, Folder 19)
    - Material from Office File, 1976-1977 (Box 261, Folder 20)
    - Membership List 1977: Notes and Correspondence (Box 261, Folder 21)
    - Membership List 1977: Printout (Box 261, Folder 22)
    - National File, 1952-1969 (Box 261, Folder 23)
    - NLG v. Brownell Material [I], 1953-1954 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - NLG v. Brownell Material [II], 1953-1954 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - NLG v. Brownell Material, 1954-1955 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - NLG v. Brownell Material, 1955-1980 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - NLG v. Brownell Material: Interrogatories and Responses, 1954 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - NLG v. Brownell Material: Interrogatory Material, 1937-1977 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - NLG Officers, 1956-1968, 1984 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters, 1976, Undated (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Present Activities, 1977 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Property of NLG (1966-1969), 1964-1971 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Report on Lawyers Guild Activities, 1949-1960 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Structure 1937-1963, 1950-1977 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Structure 1964-1969, 1964-1976 (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Structure 1970-1975, 1970-1976 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Washington DC Chapter, 1973-1977 (Box 262, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: Legal and Factual, Formal File.
    - Legal: Banks, 1976 (Box 262, Folder 16)
    - Legal: Civil Service Applicants (NLG Members), 1981 (Box 262, Folder 17)
    - Legal: Class Action, 1945-1978, Undated (Box 262, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Concealment, 1962-1981, Undated (Box 262, Folder 19)
    - Legal: Depositions, 1955-1958 (Box 262, Folder 20)
    - Legal: Discovery Non-Compliance, 1971-1980, Undated (Box 262, Folder 21)
    - Legal: Estate of W.C. Sullivan, 1978, Undated (Box 262, Folder 22)
    - Legal: House Un-American Activities Committee (HUAC) Claims, 1942-1984 (Box 262, Folder 23)
    - Legal: Informants, 1984-1985, Undated (Box 262, Folder 24)
    - Legal: International Association of Democratic Lawyers (IADL), 1947, 1951 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Interrogatories, Undated (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Justification Defense, 1965-1983, Undated (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Justification Defense - Clavir, Judith et al v. USA, 1977-1980 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Legal: New York Tort Law, 1983 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Privacy, Undated (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Research Assistance, 1982 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Legal: Rule 53, 1938-1983 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Statute of Limitations Motion, 1978, Undated (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Summary Judgment, Military Agencies, Undated (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Legal: Various Topics, 1976-1983, Undated (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Factual: Attorneys for Treason, 1975, Undated (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Factual: Bailey's Thesis - a Political History of the NLG from 1936 through the McCarthy Era [I], Undated (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - Factual: Bailey's Thesis [II], Undated (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Factual: Bailey's Thesis [III], Undated (Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Factual: Chapter Interrogatory Responses, 1977 (Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Factual: Chicago Police, 1973-1980, Undated (Box 263, Folder 17)
    - Factual: COINTELPRO, 1976-1977 (Box 263, Folder 18)
    - Factual: Committee for Legal Assistance in the South (CLAS/CASL), 1962-1964, 1982 (Box 263, Folder 19)
    - Factual: Detroit, Michigan State Police File [I], 1959-1982, Undated (Box 263, Folder 20)
    - Factual: Detroit, Michigan State Police File [II], 1959-1982, Undated (Box 263, Folder 21)
    - Factual: Detroit, Michigan State Police File [III], 1959-1982, Undated (Box 263, Folder 22)
    - Factual: Electronic Surveillance Affidavits, 1978-1980 (Box 263, Folder 23)
    - Factual: FBI Agents to Depose, 1979, Undated (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Factual: Guild Investigative Group, 1976-1977 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Factual: Guild Litigation Printout, 1982 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Factual: History of Suit, 1976-1977 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Factual: Indexes, Undated (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Factual: Informer Jo Cook, Undated (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Factual: International Association of Democratic Lawyers (IADL), 1946-1981 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Factual: June [I], 1950-1979 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Factual: June [II], 1950-1979 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Factual: Legal Services, 1976-1977 (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - Factual: Record, Interrogatory Response Requests, 1977 (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Factual: Records Destruction, 1975-1979 (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Factual: Reeses (John and S. Louise), 1976-1983 (Box 264, Folder 13)
    - Factual: Swearingen, Wesley [I], 1970-1979, Undated (Box 264, Folder 14)
    - Factual: Swearingen, Wesley [II], 1970-1979, Undated (Box 264, Folder 15)
    - Factual: Various, 1975-1978, Undated (Box 264, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Other.
    - Associational Privacy, Undated (Box 264, Folder 17)
    - Attorney General / Federal Bureau of Investigation (AG/FBI) Guidelines, 1973-1976 (Box 264, Folder 18)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines, 1977-1978 (Box 264, Folder 19)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines, 1979-May 1980 (Box 264, Folder 20)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines, Oct 1980-Nov 1980 (Box 264, Folder 21)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines, Dec 1980-1981 (Box 264, Folder 22)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines, Jan 1983-Mar 1983 (Box 264, Folder 23)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines, Apr 1983-1985, Undated (Box 264, Folder 24)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines: GAO Audit Reports [I], 1983 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines: GAO Audit Reports [II], 1983 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - AG/FBI Guidelines: General Surveillance Groups, 1982-1983, Undated (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - CIA Interrogatories, 1976, 1979, Undated (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Material, 1944-1952 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Material, 1955-1977, Undated (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Counterintelligence Programs, 1942-1971 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Counterintelligence Programs, 1981, Undated (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Destruction of Informants' Files, Undated (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Information Digest, 1969, Undated (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Information Digest, Jan 1970-Jul 1970 (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Information Digest, Aug 1970-Dec 1970 (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Information Digest, Feb 1971-Jul 1971 (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - Information Digest, Sep 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 265, Folder 14)
    - Information Digest, Jan 1972-May 1972 (Box 265, Folder 15)
    - Information Digest, Jun 1972-Sep 1972 (Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Information Digest, Oct 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 265, Folder 17)
    - Information Digest, Feb 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Information Digest, Sep 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Information Digest, Jan 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Information Digest, Jul 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Information Digest, Jan 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Information Digest, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Information Digest, 1976, 1979 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Information Digest, 1980, 1981 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Mail Covers, 1979 (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Personal Jurisdictional, 1971-1978, Undated (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Possible Agents in NLG, 1976-1977 (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Publications and Clippings, 1983-1984, Undated (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Recusal and Peter K. Leisure (USDC Judge) [I], 1969-1984 (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Recusal and Peter K. Leisure (USDC Judge) [II], 1969-1984 (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Various, 1968-1985, Undated (Box 266, Folder 15)
  - Subseries D: Litigation.
    - Related Cases: Albertson, Lillie v. USA, 1986 (Box 266, Folder 16)
    - Related Cases: Allen v. USA and CIA, 1981 (Box 266, Folder 17)
    - Related Cases: American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, 1976-1977 (Box 266, Folder 18)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, 1978 (Box 266, Folder 19)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, 1979-1980 (Box 266, Folder 20)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, Jan 8, 1980 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, Jan 9, 1980 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago, Feb 27, 1980 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago, Mar 12, 1980 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, Mar 1980-1981 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago [I], 1983 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago [II], 1983 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, 1984 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Related Cases: ACLU v. City of Chicago / Alliance to End Repression v. City of Chicago, Undated (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Related Cases: American Friends Service Committee v. Webster, 1980 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Related Cases: Bergman, Walter and Frances v. Barrett G. Kemp, 1982 (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Related Cases: Coalition against Police Abuse et al. v. Board of Police Commissioners et al., 1984 (Box 267, Folder 12)
    - Related Cases: Dodd, Thomas J. v. Drew Pearson and Jack Anderson, 1966 (Box 267, Folder 13)
    - Related Cases: Fine v. City of New York, 1975-1977 (Box 267, Folder 14)
    - Related Cases: Forsyth, Keith v. Richard G. Kleindienst et al., 1982 (Box 267, Folder 15)
    - Related Cases: Founding Church of Scientology, Washington D.C. v. FBI, 1983 (Box 267, Folder 16)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms, 1977, 1981 (Box 267, Folder 17)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms - Document Appendix [I], [1982] (Box 267, Folder 18)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms - Document Appendix [II], [1982] (Box 267, Folder 19)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms - Joint Appendix Vol. I [I], [1982] (Box 267, Folder 20)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms - Joint Appendix Vol. I [II], [1982] (Box 267, Folder 21)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms - Joint Appendix Vol. II [I], [1982] (Box 267, Folder 22)
    - Related Cases: Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms - Joint Appendix Vol. II [II], [1982] (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Related Cases: National Committee Against Repressive Litigation (NCARL) v. FBI [I], 1980 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI [II], 1980 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI [I], 1981 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI [II], 1981 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI, Exhibits [I], 1981 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI, Exhibits [II], 1981 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI [I], 1982 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI [II], 1982 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI, 1983 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI, 1984 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI, 1985 (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - Related Cases: NCARL v. FBI, 1986-1988 (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - Related Cases: National Lawyers Guild v. William Pierce Rogers, Attorney General, 1958 (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - Related Cases: Neely, Doris C. v. Central Intelligence Agency, 1982 (Box 268, Folder 15)
    - Related Cases: "Organizing Notes", 1978-1980 (Box 268, Folder 16)
    - Related Cases: "Organizing Notes", 1981-1983 (Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Related Cases: Salisbury, Harrison E. v. USA, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA [I], 1975-1982, Undated (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA [II], 1975-1982, Undated (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA [III], 1975-1982, Undated (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA [IV], 1975-1982, Undated (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA [V], 1975-1982, Undated (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Deposition Transcript, Feb 4, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Trial Transcripts, May 1, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Trial Transcripts, May 19, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Trial Trancripts, May 21, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Trial Transcripts, Jun 3, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Trial Transcripts, Jun 10, 1981 (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - Related Cases: Socialist Workers Party v. USA - Post-Trial Memorandum, 1982 (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - Related Cases: Spartacist League et al. v. Attorney General et al., 1982-1984 (Box 269, Folder 14)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray, Apr 1978-Jun 12, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray [I], May 1978 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray [II], May 1978 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray, Jun 15, 1978-Jun 21, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray [I], Aug 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray [II], Aug 1978-Oct 1978 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray, Nov 1978, Undated (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray - Dockets, 1978-1979 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Gray - Transcripts, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Related Cases: USA v. Humphrey, 1978-1979 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Political Cases: Butler, Willis P. v. USA, 1973 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Political Cases: Cherrytree, Paula et al. v. Richard Milhous Nixon et al., 1974 (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Political Cases: Cherrytree, Paula et al. v. Richard Milhous Nixon et al. - Complaint [I], 1974 (Box 270, Folder 13)
    - Political Cases: Cherrytree, Paula et al. v. Richard Milhous Nixon et al. - Complaint [II], 1974 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - Political Cases: Clark, Judith, 1979 (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - Political Cases: Dillon, Thomas C. et al. v. Gerald R. Ford et al. [I], 1976 (Box 270, Folder 16)
    - Political Cases: Dillon, Thomas C. et al. v. Gerald R. Ford et al. [II], 1976 (Box 270, Folder 17)
    - Political Cases: Ellison, Ella, [1974] (Box 270, Folder 18)
    - Political Cases: Fonda, Jane v. Richard M. Nixon et al., 1973-1974 (Box 270, Folder 19)
    - Political Cases: Gordon, Duncan v. Klassen, 1969-1972 (Box 270, Folder 20)
    - Political Cases: Grove Press v. CIA, 1975-1979 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Political Cases: Indian Affairs and Public Lands, 1977 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Political Cases: Kaufman, Marcella P. v. Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, 1975 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Political Cases: Kessler, Stephen, [1975] (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Political Cases: Military Rejections ( Security Clearance), 1966-1974, Undated (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Political Cases: New York Times v. Dena Kleiman and Hon. John R. Starkey, 1976 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Political Cases: People of the State of California v. David Hilliard, 1972 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Political Cases: People of the State of California v. D. L. Kolis, 1973 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Political Cases: People of the State of California v. Wendy Masako Yoshimura, 1977 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Political Cases: People of the State of Illinois v. Thomas K. Stewart, 1979 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Political Cases: Problems with Being Denied Facilities, 1972 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Political Cases: Rao, Paul P. v. Nelson Rockefeller et al., 1977 (Box 271, Folder 12)
    - Political Cases: Rice, David and Edward Poindexter, 1969-1979, Undated (Box 271, Folder 13)
    - Political Cases: Rosen, Sol Z. and Local 6 of the Newspaper and Graphic Communication Union, 1975-1976 (Box 271, Folder 14)
    - Political Cases: USA v. Carlos Avila, 1976 (Box 271, Folder 15)
    - Political Cases: USA v. H. R. Haldeman (Watergate), 1972 (Box 271, Folder 16)
    - Political Cases: USA v. H. R. Haldeman (Watergate), 1973 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - Political Cases: USA v. H. R. Haldeman (Watergate), 1975 (Box 271, Folder 18)
    - Political Cases: Wilmington 10, [1974] (Box 271, Folder 19)
    - Reeses (John and Louise Rees), Related Litigation: Articles, Publications and Other Materials Associated with the Reeses, 1973-1982 (Box 271, Folder 20)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Correspondence, 1976-1977, 1983 (Box 271, Folder 21)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Court Documents (Formal File) [I], 1976-1977 (Box 271, Folder 22)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Court Documents (Formal File) [II], 1976-1977 (Box 271, Folder 23)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Deposition, 1977 (Box 271, Folder 24)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Interrogatories - Supplement, 1976-1977 (Box 271, Folder 25)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Notes, 1972-1988, Undated (Box 271, Folder 26)
    - Reeses, Related Litigation: Research, 1977, 1982, Undated (Box 271, Folder 27)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Attorney General v. The Irish People, Inc., 1974, 1978 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Bishop, Kay et al v. Reagan-Bush '84 Committee et al., 1984 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Blair, Mary v. F. J. Baumgardner et al., 1979 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Brown, Ted W. et al. v. Socialist Workers '74 Campaign Committee (Ohio) et al., 1982 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Chicago Contempt, USA v. Dellinger et al., 1972, Undated (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Dellinger v. Mitchell, 1969-1974 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Dellinger v. Mitchell, 1975-1978 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Dellinger v. Mitchell, 1979, Undated (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Dellinger v. Mitchell - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Dellinger v. Mitchell - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Fonda, Jane v. L. Patrick Gray et al., 1979 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Jabara, Abdeen M. v. Clarence Kelly et al., 1974 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Kinoy, Joanne et al. v. John N. Mitchell et al., 1974 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Philadelphia Resistance v. John N. Mitchell, 1975 (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - USA v. William Ayers et al., 1974 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - USA v. Veronza Bowers and Alan Veale, 1973-1975 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Weinberg, Doran et al. v. John N. Mitchell et al. [I], 1975-1979 (Box 272, Folder 17)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Weinberg, Doran et al. v. John N. Mitchell et al. [II], 1975-1979 (Box 272, Folder 18)
    - Other Cases of Interest: Electronic Surveillance - Weinberg, Doran et al. v. John N. Mitchell et al. [III], 1975-1979 (Box 272, Folder 19)